AGUSTIN SAMPIETRO

sampietroagustin@gmail.com - LinkedIn - GitHub

SUMMARY

Mobile Application Developer with more than 13 years of experience. I started working as an Android Developer using Java as my first Mobile Technology for around 5 years and then I went through NativeScript with Angular, TypeScript and NodeJS for almost 2 years and I'm currently working as a Flutter Developer since 2019. Skilled, motivated and product-oriented mobile application developer with strong Object Oriented Programming concepts and agile methodologies.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Mobile Developer at Co-Diagnostics Inc January 2021 to present (contractor)

Flutter Developer (Android, IOS and Web). Skills: Riverpod, GraphQL, Firebase, QR Reader, Bluetooth Connection.

Mobile Developer at Idaho Molecular Inc February 2021 to December 2021 (contractor)

Flutter Developer (Android, IOS and Web). Skills: BLoC, GraphQL, Firebase, QR Reader, Bluetooth Connection.

Product Owner at D.S.A. srl June 2016 to February 2021

PO in Mobile projects. Leading a team of 5 people. Activities: analysis, design and mobile development.

Mobile Developer at D.S.A. srl June 2011 to February 2021

Several projects. Skills used: Mobile: AndroidStudio (Java), NativeScript, Flutter, FireBase. Web: .NET, JavaScript, RestAPI. Data Base: SQL, MySQL, SQLite.

Android development at Emser

April 2012 - February 2013 Android Application Developer at Emser S.A. Android developer an application for Arcor S.A. (to sell products).

FREELANCE EXPERIENCE

Last projects and skills used:

- Golfito (Freelance) App to take the metrics of each game and player (Flutter, C# Backend, FireBase Integration). Google Play App Store
- Worktra Product owner and mobile developer (Flutter). Google Play App Store
- Glib Mobile developer (Flutter). VideoCall included Google Play App Store
- TareaYa (Freelance) Full Stack Developer (Flutter, C# Backend). App that connects professionals who
 want to offer their services with users who need help. <u>Google Play App Store</u>

EDUCATION

- February 2014 to 2015 Embassy CES (San Francisco, CA) General English
- 2011 to 2013 Universidad Empresarial 'Siglo 21' systems engineering in software.
- 2008 2011 IES siglo 21 Computer Systems Analyst in software and technology.

LANGUAGES Spanish - Level: Native English - Level: Advanced

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Desire to contribute to the advancement of company goals and growth using personal knowledge and new abilities learned
- Eager to learn and improve new abilities and technologies
- High ability to work in group and alone

SKILLS AND KNOWLEDGE

- Flutter, Dart, JavaScript, Firebase, Java, C#, Rest API, GraphQL, BLoC, Providers, Riverpod, Ble Connection, Camera, GPS, Git, Jira, GitHub, BitBucker, Java, AndroidStudio, XCode, GooglePlay, AppStore, Figma.
- Agile methodologies, scrum, integration with clients, technical leader, product owner, problem solver.